<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Defs>
    <XenotypeDef>
        <defName>Xenotype_RakkleBase</defName>
        <label>rakkle</label>
		<description>Rakkles are reptilian humanoids originally found on a remote planet in the Rim.
			After their discovery, human colonies rounded them up and genetically altered them to
			have near-human intelligence, but also decreased aggression and appearances better
			suited to human tastes. They were also modified to give birth to females more often than
			males, creating a biological need for species interbreeding.\n\nThe newly created Rakkle
			species were managed by a company known as The Cradle beyond the reaches of the galaxy,
			while wild Rakkle were hunted and killed to protect the company's interest. Future
			generations within the facilities were conditioned and raised as slaves and
			livestock.\n\n After a series of escapes and revolts on planet after planet, a coalition
			of freed Rakkle began colonies of their own, resisting capture and invasion to create a
			new world where Rakkle can live outside the yoke of slavery. Despite The Cradle's best
			efforts, these settlements continue to grow in size and number.</description>
		<descriptionShort>Rakkles are reptilian humanoids originally found on a remote planet in the
			Rim. After their discovery, human colonies rounded them up and genetically altered them
			to have near-human intelligence, but also decreased aggression and appearances better
			suited to human tastes. They were also modified to give birth to females more often than
			males, creating a biological need for species interbreeding.\n\nThe newly created Rakkle
			species were managed by a company known as The Cradle beyond the reaches of the galaxy,
			while wild Rakkle were hunted and killed to protect the company's interest. Future
			generations within the facilities were conditioned and raised as slaves and
			livestock.\n\n After a series of escapes and revolts on planet after planet, a coalition
			of freed Rakkle began colonies of their own, resisting capture and invasion to create a
			new world where Rakkle can live outside the yoke of slavery. Despite The Cradle's best
			efforts, these settlements continue to grow in size and number.</descriptionShort>
		<iconPath>Icon/RakkleXenotype</iconPath>
        <inheritable>true</inheritable>
        <genes>
            <li>Hair_DarkBlack</li>
            <li>Hair_DarkBrown</li>
            <li>Hair_Gray</li>

            <li>Skin_LightGray</li>
            <li>Skin_SheerWhite</li>

            <li>RV2_TypeEnabler_Tailmaw</li>
            <li>RV2_TypeEnabler_Oral</li>
            <li>RV2_TypeEnabler_Vaginal</li>

            <li>RV2_GoalEnabler_Digest</li>
            <li>RV2_GoalEnabler_ConvertLube</li>
            <li>RV2_GoalEnabler_Reform</li>
        </genes>
        <factionlessGenerationWeight>0.00001</factionlessGenerationWeight>
    </XenotypeDef>

</Defs>